Guide to the Debra Danburg Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Media
  - PRIDE ‘02 magazine, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Texas Monthly, 1988-1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Texas Monthly, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Herald-Voice, 1999 (Ovs box 10, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Herald-Voice, 2000 (Ovs box 10, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Herald-Voice, 2001 (Ovs box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Jewish Herald-Voice, 2002 (Ovs box 10, Folder 5)
  - Texas Triangle, 1999 (Ovs box 10, Folder 6)
  - Texas Triangle, 2000 (Ovs box 10, Folder 7)
  - Houston Realtor, 2002 (Ovs box 10, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous oversized magazines, 2000 (Ovs box 10, Folder 9)
- Events
  - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - February-April 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - June-October 1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 2000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 2002 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Legislature
  - Voting records, 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Voting records, 1991-2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - List of bills, 1981-1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 74th legislature, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 75th legislature (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Accomplishments, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Accomplishments, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Accomplishments, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Accomplishments, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Accomplishments, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sexual orientation and gender bias issues, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Analysis of bills, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Reports and questionnaire, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Speeches
  - Lobbying, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - AIDS, Speech info, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Women’s movement, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - UH convocation, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Electric utility restructuring, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Electric utility restructuring, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Candidate forum on arts, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - TMHA Houston, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Health legislation seminar, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Mayor’s access speech, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Houston mortgage banker’s assn., 2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Houston human resources assn., 2001 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fuel cell initiative, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Speech etiquette, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Electric Utility Restucturing
  - Delegation to California – Agenda, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Delegation to California – PUC information, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Delegation to California – AB 1890 and analysis, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Delegation to California – Articles, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Delegation to California – Glossary, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Delegation to Pennsylvania – Agenda, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Delegation to Pennsylvania – PUC briefing, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Delegation to Pennsylvania – Summaries of PA model, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Delegation to Pennsylvania – De-regulation legislation, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Delegation to Pennsylvania – Articles, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Delegation to Pennsylvania – Consumer education, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Texas Industrial Energy conference, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Legislative outline, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Bill analysis, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Enrolled bill, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - C.S.S.B No. 7, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Presentations – S.B 7, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Presentations, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Presentations – Market structure, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Presentations – Cost recovery, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Presentations – Jess Totten, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Presentations – Greater Houston representation, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Campaign
  - Printed Campaign originals, 1990-2002 (Box 6, Folder 53-54)
- Resources
  - Greater Montrose Business Guild Directories and Media Guide, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Greater Montrose Business Guild Directory, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - This Week in Texas, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - This Week in Texas, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - This Week in Texas, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gay/Lesbian Yellow Pages, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Gay/Lesbian Yellow Pages, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Resource guide, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Legal services guide, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Houston Bar Association Directory, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Photographs
  - Capitol photographs, 1981-2002 (Box 7, Folder 11-22)
  - Press Conferences, 1981-2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Governor Ann Richards State of the State address, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Stalking bill signing, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bill signing, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bill signing and Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Headshots, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - With Republicans, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - With former president Clinton and others, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - With Mark Stiles, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - With Speaker Billy Clayton, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous – Capitol and others, undated (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - Fundraiser photo shoot, undated (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
  - Campaign photographs, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Campaign photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - With Judge Eckels and Slate, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - With Senator Ellis, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - UH Law center, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Volleyball game, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous party, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - From Bill Best, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Montrose clinic ribbon cutting and camping photos, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Celebrity waiters, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Breast feeding day, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Republic waste services, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Heights fest, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Buffalo bayou canoeing, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - With E.Os, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Family photographs, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Birthday party and Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Holiday, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Family photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Family photographs and holiday, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Holiday and miscellaneous, undated (Box 8, Folder 34-36)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8, Folder 37-42)
  - Negatives – Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8, Folder 43-45)
  - Negatives – Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Slides – Headshots, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous
  - Correspondence, 1981-2002 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum vita, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Certificates, 1996-2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cards, 1991-2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cartoons and caricatures, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Paul Bettencourt tax assessment report, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Ephemera
  - Pins
    - Macho is Sicko, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Some leaders are born women, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Napalm squad, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Let the people decide, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Having abandoned my search for Truth……., undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Value all families, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Re-elect Ron Walters, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Women who seek to be equal to men lack ambition, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Jane Wyman was right, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Freeking wood, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Gib Lewis day, January 11 1983 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - I didn’t go on – Claytie’s bunny hunt, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - I’m a mini feminist, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Equal partnership in marriage, undated (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
    - Motherhood by choice not by chance, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Sunset the farm bureau, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Sex Without Partners, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - I trust the women of my state to decide, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - An army of lovers can’t fail, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Minds are like parachutes – they only function when open, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Glen Maxey for state representative, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Kingwood: Houston as Rancho Santa Fe: San Diego, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Health insurance – As good as the Governor’s, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Question Authority, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Say Yes to life and NO to drugs, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Austin Aqua Festival skipper, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - November. 4 Yes Prop. 8 Home equity reform, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Cotton boll weevil, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Support long-term care in Texas, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Stop hate crimes, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - We don’t need balls to play, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Hitler McCarthy Falwell, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Neartown is positively unique, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - How dare you presume I would rather be young, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Prevent divorce, stay single, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Danburg, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Have you hugged your dad today?, undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - A family by choice is a family, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Women are not a single issue, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Sexism is not a social disease, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Debra Danburg for state representative (On Cap), undated (Box 11, Folder 42-43)
    - Sissy (On Cap), undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Rudd’s Raiders (On Cap), undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Gerry Ferraro – America’s first women VP (On Cap), undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous items
    - Sticker - Debra, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Sticker - America, Let’s roll, undated (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Sticker - Texas – State of the arts, undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Sticker - Save the males, undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Sticker - If you can’t trust me with a choice…….., undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Pen (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Envelope opener (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Beads (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Cap (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Texas state official license plate (Box 11, Folder 56-57)
    - Official identification card – 72nd legislature, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Framed photographs
    - Danburg with baby, undated (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
    - For Debra…… from Steve, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
    - UH Law Center, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Houston Community College, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 1948 San Jacinto hockey team (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Capitol photos, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
    - Capitol photos, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 11-14)
    - Capitol photos, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
    - Capitol photos, undated (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 12, Folder 19-22)
  - Posters
    - House of Representatives – 74th legislature, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - The story of Texas, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Out Beyond – Urban air space exhibition, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Southwest voter registration education project, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Disks
    - Restructuring utilities floppy disk, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Legislative accomplishments – 73rd to 77th, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Photos, undated (Box 12, Folder 29-30)
    - UH Degree certificate folder, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 31)